[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Vermont reeling from the worst flooding since the '20s, but was Irene overblown?", "question_tokens": ["Vermont", "reeling", "from", "the", "worst", "flooding", "since", "the", "'20s", ",", "but", "was", "Irene", "overblown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Clearly, this could have been worse, but it was pretty bad out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Clearly", ",", "this", "could", "have", "been", "worse", ",", "but", "it", "was", "pretty", "bad", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'20s"], "PERSON": ["Irene"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Did government and the media go too far?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "government", "and", "the", "media", "go", "too", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Better to be safe than sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["Better", "to", "be", "safe", "than", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vermont"]}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Did people know what may be coming?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "people", "know", "what", "may", "be", "coming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, first of all, there is a lot of resentment here in Vermont when people say this was hyped.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "is", "a", "lot", "of", "resentment", "here", "in", "Vermont", "when", "people", "say", "this", "was", "hyped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJR", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "What was the general feeling about the scenes that we are witnessing and the possible casualty toll?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "general", "feeling", "about", "the", "scenes", "that", "we", "are", "witnessing", "and", "the", "possible", "casualty", "toll", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "UCHMAN: We don't think it will go much higher, but we do think it will go higher.", "answer_tokens": ["UCHMAN", ":", "We", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "will", "go", "much", "higher", ",", "but", "we", "do", "think", "it", "will", "go", "higher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Winooski", "Lake Champlain", "Connecticut River Basin"]}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "When you see what's happening in Vermont, what do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "what", "'s", "happening", "in", "Vermont", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Obviously our heart goes out to the victims who are in the affected areas both on the west side of the state in those tributaries like the Winooski that feed into Lake Champlain and on the east of the state in the Connecticut River Basin.", "answer_tokens": ["Obviously", "our", "heart", "goes", "out", "to", "the", "victims", "who", "are", "in", "the", "affected", "areas", "both", "on", "the", "west", "side", "of", "the", "state", "in", "those", "tributaries", "like", "the", "Winooski", "that", "feed", "into", "Lake", "Champlain", "and", "on", "the", "east", "of", "the", "state", "in", "the", "Connecticut", "River", "Basin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vermont"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What do you say to those who say that the media, including CNN and others, hyped up this hurricane and that it wasn't as bad as everyone said it was going to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "who", "say", "that", "the", "media", ",", "including", "CNN", "and", "others", ",", "hyped", "up", "this", "hurricane", "and", "that", "it", "was", "n't", "as", "bad", "as", "everyone", "said", "it", "was", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, I think it's a partial truth that is fundamentally inaccurate though at its base.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "partial", "truth", "that", "is", "fundamentally", "inaccurate", "though", "at", "its", "base", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Irene"]}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "But in terms of how the power and the strength and therefore the threat of Hurricane Irene changing in that very crucial last 24 hours, could that have been predicted at all or can the authorities only really ever go on what's right in front of them at any given moment?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "terms", "of", "how", "the", "power", "and", "the", "strength", "and", "therefore", "the", "threat", "of", "Hurricane", "Irene", "changing", "in", "that", "very", "crucial", "last", "24", "hours", ",", "could", "that", "have", "been", "predicted", "at", "all", "or", "can", "the", "authorities", "only", "really", "ever", "go", "on", "what", "'s", "right", "in", "front", "of", "them", "at", "any", "given", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "MD", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "The problem with Irene is that for wind it was an underachiever.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "problem", "with", "Irene", "is", "that", "for", "wind", "it", "was", "an", "underachiever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Weather Service"]}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What is your view from an official point of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "from", "an", "official", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, from an official point of view, we really had to make decisions based on what we were hearing from the National Weather Service and other hurricane and governmental experts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "from", "an", "official", "point", "of", "view", ",", "we", "really", "had", "to", "make", "decisions", "based", "on", "what", "we", "were", "hearing", "from", "the", "National", "Weather", "Service", "and", "other", "hurricane", "and", "governmental", "experts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "How would you respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "You know, the snow response was absolutely an unacceptable response.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "snow", "response", "was", "absolutely", "an", "unacceptable", "response", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes, I was down in Nags Head feeling the winds a couple of days ago and I was still finding sand in my hair and my ears this morning.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "was", "down", "in", "Nags", "Head", "feeling", "the", "winds", "a", "couple", "of", "days", "ago", "and", "I", "was", "still", "finding", "sand", "in", "my", "hair", "and", "my", "ears", "this", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "How many have to be killed before you assess this as serious enough to take the measures they took?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "have", "to", "be", "killed", "before", "you", "assess", "this", "as", "serious", "enough", "to", "take", "the", "measures", "they", "took", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "No, Piers, that's not what I'm saying.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What do you have to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "have", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "I have looked at all the other storms that were the same pressure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "looked", "at", "all", "the", "other", "storms", "that", "were", "the", "same", "pressure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Faced with the exactly same set of circumstances, would you do exactly the same thing again?", "question_tokens": ["Faced", "with", "the", "exactly", "same", "set", "of", "circumstances", ",", "would", "you", "do", "exactly", "the", "same", "thing", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Is it a different thing when you're dealing with a hurricane with mass flooding and so on?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "different", "thing", "when", "you", "'re", "dealing", "with", "a", "hurricane", "with", "mass", "flooding", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, remember, social media is a great tool.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "remember", ",", "social", "media", "is", "a", "great", "tool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Look, I'm a person of faith.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "person", "of", "faith", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "You're going to raise hell, have you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "going", "to", "raise", "hell", ",", "have", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "That's true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Yeah, 40.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "40", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What would you prefer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "prefer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "You know, I like my jet.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "like", "my", "jet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "That's the American way, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "American", "way", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "It's the American way.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "American", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Is it ethically right that he should be able to do this, given what he was found guilty of?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "ethically", "right", "that", "he", "should", "be", "able", "to", "do", "this", ",", "given", "what", "he", "was", "found", "guilty", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "America loves second chances.", "answer_tokens": ["America", "loves", "second", "chances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "If you could have signed him, would you have done?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "have", "signed", "him", ",", "would", "you", "have", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Would you have had any moral problem with it?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "had", "any", "moral", "problem", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "You know, I try to get to know our guys.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "try", "to", "get", "to", "know", "our", "guys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Any knuckleheads on your current team?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "knuckleheads", "on", "your", "current", "team", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I'm not allowed to talk about my current team.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "allowed", "to", "talk", "about", "my", "current", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "is she really?", "question_tokens": ["is", "she", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "What do you think of that, as a former contender yourself.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", ",", "as", "a", "former", "contender", "yourself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "What's the business ethos of Mark Cuban?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "business", "ethos", "of", "Mark", "Cuban", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I learned that -- you know, I started with nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "learned", "that", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "started", "with", "nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Can they e- mail you if they watch this?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "they", "e-", "mail", "you", "if", "they", "watch", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Mark@hd.net.", "answer_tokens": ["Mark", "@", "hd.net", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "How quickly do you respond?", "question_tokens": ["How", "quickly", "do", "you", "respond", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I read them first.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "read", "them", "first", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "When do you immediately delete?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "you", "immediately", "delete", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "The minute they start with a sob story.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "minute", "they", "start", "with", "a", "sob", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "What's been your biggest failure?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "your", "biggest", "failure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "goodness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "If you are not willing to put in the effort, if you're not willing to commit everything, why would I invest in you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "are", "not", "willing", "to", "put", "in", "the", "effort", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "not", "willing", "to", "commit", "everything", ",", "why", "would", "I", "invest", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Going to take a little break.", "answer_tokens": ["Going", "to", "take", "a", "little", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Are you prepared to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "prepared", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Done.", "answer_tokens": ["Done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Is he like Ari Gold?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "like", "Ari", "Gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "No quite, but he's intense.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "quite", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "intense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "UBAN: No, it's not right.", "answer_tokens": ["UBAN", ":", "No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Do you think he's given America that or has he failed America?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "given", "America", "that", "or", "has", "he", "failed", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "He's failed, but not through faults of his own.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "failed", ",", "but", "not", "through", "faults", "of", "his", "own", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Who of the Republican candidates do you think could make potentially a president?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "of", "the", "Republican", "candidates", "do", "you", "think", "could", "make", "potentially", "a", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "They all could make a president.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "all", "could", "make", "a", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Who would make a good one?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "make", "a", "good", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "None of them yet, because -- all for the same reason.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "of", "them", "yet", ",", "because", "--", "all", "for", "the", "same", "reason", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "kidding", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "You have done everything else.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "done", "everything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Looking back at it, how did it feel to you?", "question_tokens": ["Looking", "back", "at", "it", ",", "how", "did", "it", "feel", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "It was amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "The moment you knew you had won, what was going through your head?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "you", "knew", "you", "had", "won", ",", "what", "was", "going", "through", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "There's actually -- I watched the video, and I just screamed.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "actually", "--", "I", "watched", "the", "video", ",", "and", "I", "just", "screamed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Did you think of anybody?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "of", "anybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I thought of my dad.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "of", "my", "dad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "If enough Americans decided they quite like Mark Cuban to work his magic on America that he's worked for the Mavericks, what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "enough", "Americans", "decided", "they", "quite", "like", "Mark", "Cuban", "to", "work", "his", "magic", "on", "America", "that", "he", "'s", "worked", "for", "the", "Mavericks", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "I'm not going to buy another sports team.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "buy", "another", "sports", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I am absolutely serious.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "absolutely", "serious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Can we expert the little patter of little Beyonce and Jay-Zs?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "expert", "the", "little", "patter", "of", "little", "Beyonce", "and", "Jay-Zs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Only God knows.", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "God", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"]}}]